Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
-=xXSwesubsXx=-
Kinda lonesome back here.
Yeah, little help.
Okay, just, I have to keep my hands
on the wheel.
Excuse me.
Dopinder.
Pool. Dead.
Nice.
Smells good, no?
Not the Daffodil Daydream. The girl.
Yes. Gita. She is quite lovely.
She would have made me
a very agreeable wife.
But, Gita's heart has been stolen
by my cousin Bandhu.
He is as dishonorable
as he is attractive.
Dopinder, I'm starting to think
there's a reason I'm in this cab today.
Yeah, sir, you called for it, remember?
No, my slender brown friend.
Love is a beautiful thing.
When you find it, the whole world
tastes like Daffodil Daydream.
So you gotta hold onto love...
tight!
And never let go.
Don't make the same mistakes I did.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Or else the whole world tastes
like Mama June after hot yoga.
Sir, what does Miss Mama June
taste like?
- Like two hobos fucking in a shoe filled with piss.
- Okay, enough.
I can go all day, Dopinder.
The point is, it's bad!
It's bad.
Why the fancy red suit, Mr. Pool?
That's because it's Christmas Day,
Dopinder.
And I'm after someone on my naughty list.
I've been waiting one year, three weeks...
six days and...
14 minutes to make him fix
what he did to me.
And what did he do to you, Mr. Pool?
This shit...
Boo!
They won't disappoint.
They'd better not.
And what about next month's shipment?
There won't be one.
You're not the only one
with a war to win.
That won't do.
See, we've had this small disruption
to our supply chain...
We'd appreciate your patience.
Okay.
We'll deliver in full the following month.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Fucking mutant.
Ah, shit!
I forgot my ammo bag.
- Shall we turn back?
- No, no time.
Fuck it. I got this.
9, 10, 11, 12 bullets, or bust.
Right here!
That's $27.50.
I never carry a wallet when I'm working.
Ruins the lines of my suit.
But, how about a crisp high five?
Okay.
Merry Christmas.
And a convivial Tuesday in April
to you too, Pool!
Shoop shooop ba-doop, shoop ba-doop
Shoop ba-doop, ba-doop, ba-doop
You're packed and you're stacked
'specially in the back
Brother, wanna thank your mother
for a butt like that
Can I get some fries
with that shake-shake boobie?
If looks could kill you would be an uzi
You're a shotgun - bang!
Oh, hello. I know, right?
Whose balls did I have to fondle
to get my very own movie?
I can't tell you,
but it does rhyme with "Polverine."
And let me tell you, he's got a nice pair
of smooth criminals down under.
Anyway, I got places to be,
a face to fix and...
Bad guys to kill.
Maximum effort.
Cock shot.
Rich Corinthian leather.
I'm looking for Francis!
Have you seen this man?
Yanky, yanky!
I've never said this, but don't swallow.
Shit.
Did I leave the stove on?
Now, breaking news.
A multi-car collision turned shots fired
on the crosstown expressway this morning.
Gridlock has kept police from the scene.
Residents are advised to
remain in their homes.
The assailant appears to be armed,
dangerous, and wearing...
- a red suit.
- A red suit.
Deadpool.
Negasonic! Come, we have mission.
Colossus, wait up.
I've given Deadpool every
chance to join us...
but he'd rather act like a child.
A heavily-armed child.
When will he grow up
and see benefits of becoming X-Man?
Which benefits? The matching unitards?
The house that blows up every few years?
Please.
House blowing up builds character.
You ate breakfast, yes?
Breakfast is most important meal of day.
Here, protein bar. Good for bones.
Deadpool may try to break yours.
Get out of the way!
Hey!
Wait!
You may be wondering,
"Why the red suit?"
Well, that's so bad guys
can't see me bleed.
This guy's got the right idea.
He wore the brown pants.
Fine! I only have 12 bullets...
so you're gonna have to share!
Let's count them down.
Shit.
Motherfucker!
10! Shit!
Nine. Fuck.
Eight.
Shit-fuck!
Bad Deadpool.
Seven. Good Deadpool.
Someone's not counting. Six.
Four.
Gotcha.
Right up Main Street.
Three, two!
Stupid! Worth it.
I'm touching myself tonight.
Francis!
Francis...
What the shit-biscuit!
Where you at, Francis?
You're not Francis.
Really? Rolling up the sleeves?
You're probably thinking, "My boyfriend
said this was a superhero movie...
"but that guy in the red suit just turned
that other guy into a fucking kabab!"
Well, I may be super, but I'm no hero.
And, yeah, technically, this is a murder.
But some of the best love stories
start with a murder.
And that's exactly what this is.
A love story.
And to tell it right...
I gotta take you back to long before
I squeezed this ass into red spandex.
Look, would it help if I slow it down for you?
I didn't order the pizza.
Is this 7348 Red Ledge Drive?
Are you Mr. Merchant?
Yeah, the Mr. Merchant
who didn't order the fucking pie!
Then who placed the call?
I did!
Pineapple and olive?
Sweet and salty.
The fuck are you?
The fuck you doing in my crib...
Is it burnt crust?
God, I hope not.
Man, look, if this is
about that poker game.
I told Howie, I told him that...
Okay, look, just take whatever you want.
Thanks.
Sir, before you do anything to him,
do you mind if I get a big tip?
Jeremy, is it?
Wade. Wade Wilson.
That is a no go on the tiperoo, Jer.
I'm not here for him.
I'm here for you.
Okay, wow, dodged a big-time
bullet on that one.
Not out of the woods yet.
You need to seriously ease up
on the bedazzling.
They're jeans, not a chandelier.
P.S. I'm keeping your wallet.
You did kinda give it to me.
Okay, just look, man,
can I have my Sam's card...
I will shoot your fucking cat!
I don't really know what that means.
I don't have a cat.
Then whose kitty litter did I just shit in?
Anyhoo, tell me something...
what situation isn't improved by pizza?
Do you happen to know a Meghan Orflosky?
Getting that right? Orflosky?
Orlovsky? Yeah? Good.
Because she knows you.
Jeremy, I belong to a group of guys
who take a dime to beat a fella down.
And little Meghan, she's not made of money,
but lucky for her...
I got a soft spot.
- But I'm a...
- A stalker.
Threats hurt, Jer.
Though not nearly as badly
as serrated steel.
So keep away from Meghan.
Cool?
Yes, sir.
Then we're done.
Wait. We are?
Yeah. We're totally done.
You should've seen your face.
I didn't know what to do.
I was so scared.
Soft spot, remember?
You even look
in her general direction again...
and you will learn in the worst of ways
that I have some hard spots too.
That came out wrong.
Or did it?
Meghan?
You've heard the last of Jeremy.
He's sorry.
No friggin' way.
Should've brought my roller blades.
Show these kids how it's done.
And that's why we do it.
But mostly the money.
Hey, think you could fuck up
my step-dad?
I give a guy a pavement facial,
it's because he's earned it.
Hey, wait!
You're my hero.
No-no-no-no. That I ain't!
Nope. Never will be.
Fuck you, Wade.
I'm just a bad guy
who gets paid to fuck up worse guys.
Welcome to Sister Margaret's.
It's like a job fair for mercenaries.
Think of us as really
fucked up tooth fairies...
except we knock out the teeth
and take the cash.
You'd best hope we never see
your name on a gold card.
Buck! Liefeld...
Hey, Wade!
Wade Wilson, patron saint of the pitiful.
What can I do for you?
I'd love a Blow Job.
Oh, God, me too.
The drink, moose knuckle. But first...
Hey, and I ain't taking
any babysitting money, all right?
Make sure that gets back to Ms...
Orlovsky.
Yeah, her.
You sure?
You know, for a merc,
you're pretty warm-blooded.
I bet you let the kid off easy, too.
He's not a bad kid, Weas.
Just a little light stalking.
I was way worse than him
when I was his age.
I was traveling to exotic places...
Baghdad, Mogadishu, Jacksonville,
meeting new and exciting people. And then...
Killing them.
Yeah, I've seen your Instagram.
So what was Special Forces
doing in Jacksonville, anyway?
That's classified.
They have a wonderful TGI Fridays.
All right, Kahlua, Baileys and...
whipped cream.
I give you a Blow Job.
Why do you make me make that?
Kelly, Kelly, Kelly...
Take that over to Buck, please,
and tell him it's from Boothe. Little foreplay.
Remind me what good will come of this?
I don't take the shits.
I just disturb them.
Boothe!
- Easy, man.
- Hold up! Hold up!
What you want?
- Cheers. To your health.
- Fuck you.
Come here, you fat fuck!
That's a new stool.
Stay the fuck down.
Whoa! Took his ass out!
All right, move. Move, move, move.
Buck, go rest.
Boothe got hit then went down.
Yeah, he's still breathing.
Nobody wins today.
Nice try, Wade.
You got me. I picked Boothe
in the dead pool. Who did you pick?
Yeah, Wade, about that...
No.
You did not bet on me to die.
You bet on me to die. Wow.
Motherfucker, you're the world's worst friend.
Well, joke's on you. I'm living to 102.
And then dying.
Like the city of Detroit.
I'm sorry. I just...
I wanted to win money.
I never win anything.
Whatever.
Soldiers of fortune, drinks on me!
Domestic, nothing imported.
Baby, are you sure you wanna
shoot your whole wad?
Tight.
- Vanessa.
- Wade.
What's a nice place like you
doing in a girl like this?
I'd hit that.
Buck, you best apologize before...
Yeah, that.
Say the magic words, Fat Gandalf.
- I'm sorry.
- Breathe through the nose.
I don't have a filter
between my brain and my...
Let go. Okay. Hey...
- Hakuna his tatas. He's sorry.
- I'm working on it.
Get out of here. Go. Go cast a spell.
Hey. Hands off the merchandise.
Merchandise?
So you...
bump fuzzies for money?
Yep.
Rough childhood?
Rougher than yours.
Daddy left before I was born.
Daddy left before I was conceived.
Ever had a cigarette
put out on your skin?
Where else do you put one out?
I was molested.
Me too. Uncle.
Uncles. They took turns.
I watched my own birthday party
through the keyhole of a locked closet...
which also happens to be my...
Your bedroom. Lucky.
I slept in a dishwasher box.
You had a dishwasher.
I didn't even know sleep.
It was pretty much 24/7 ball gags,
brownie mix and clown porn.
Who would do such a thing?
Hopefully you, later tonight?
Hey, what can I get for $275 and a...
a Yogurtland rewards card?
Baby, about 48 minutes
of whatever the fuck you want.
And a low-fat dessert.
Did she just put a gift card
in your mouth?
It's time to put balls in holes.
You said whatever I want.
I get it.
You love skee ball.
Apparently more than you love vagina.
That's a tough call.
I just wanna get to know
the real you, you know.
Not the short-shorted, two-dimensional
sex object peddled by Hollywood.
Balls in holes.
Prepare to lose tragically.
Bring it, big man.
Okay.
The limited edition Voltron:
Defender of the Universe ring, por favor.
Okay. Here we go.
Had my eye on this sucker for a while.
And I will take the pencil eraser.
Okay.
You are now the protector
of the planet Arus.
And you can erase stuff...
written in pencil.
M'lady?
Well, I hate to break it to you...
but your 48 minutes are up.
Hey, how many more minutes
can I get for this?
FYI, five mini lion-bots come together
to form one super-bot, so...
Five mini lion-bots? Three minutes.
Deal.
What do we do with the remaining
two minutes, 37 seconds?
Cuddle?
How long can you keep this up?
All year?
Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Chinese New Year.
Year of the Dog.
Relax.
And Happy International Women's Day.
No. No. No.
Happy Lent.
- Wade?
- Sorry.
Happy Halloween.
Happy Thanksgiving.
I love you.
If your left leg is Thanksgiving...
and your right leg is Christmas...
can I visit you between the holidays?
That sweater is terrible.
But red looks good on you.
Red's your color.
Brings out the bloodshot in your eyes.
Listen, I've been thinking...
Really?
...about why we're so good together.
Why's that?
Your crazy matches my crazy.
Big time.
And, we're like two jigsaw pieces,
you know, the weird curvy edges...
You put them together
and you can see the picture on top.
Right.
Wade...
there's something I've been
meaning to ask you.
But only because you haven't
gotten around to asking me.
Will you...
- stick it in my...
- Marry me?
Jinx?
Where were you hiding that?
Nowhere.
They say one month's salary. So...
You mean?
I do.
That's my line.
I love you, Wade Wilson.
You're supposed to...
So that's a...
Yes!
I feel just like a little girl.
What if I just held on and never let go?
Just ride a bitch's back,
like Yoda on Luke.
Star Wars jokes.
Empire.
Jesus Christ.
It's like I made you in a computer.
Hey.
Perfect.
- Let's see.
- All right, wee break.
Shake it, yeah.
Here's the thing.
Life is an endless series
of train-wrecks...
with only brief,
commercial-like breaks of happiness.
This had been the ultimate
commercial break.
Which meant it was time to return
to our regularly scheduled program.
What the...
Oh, my God. Wade?
You're clowning.
You're not clowning?
I sense clowns.
People react to news
of late-stage cancer differently.
There are certainly options we can look into.
New drugs are being developed every day.
So what do we do?
Surely there is something we can do.
My uncle Ivan was diagnosed
with thyroid cancer...
and there were all these
new experimental drugs from Germany.
Vanessa's already working on
Plan A, B, all the way through Z.
Me? I'm memorizing
the details of her face.
Like it's the first time I'm seeing it.
Or the last.
Mr. Wilson...
Mr. Wilson?
Take your time to process this.
It's important not to do anything rash.
Now, if I were a 200-pound sack of assholes
named Francis, where would I hide?
A hush falls over the crowd
as rookie sensation Wade W. Wilson...
out of Regina, Saskatchewan,
lines up the shot.
His form looks good.
And that's why Regina rhymes with fun.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what you're witnessing...
is sweet dick-kicking revenge.
Giving him the business.
Incoming!
This is taking unsportsmanlike
conduct to a whole new level!
Looking good, Francis. Well rested.
Like you've been pitching, not catching.
Ringing any bells? No?
How about now?
Wade fucking Wilson.
Well, hello, gorgeous.
Yeah, like I got bit
by a radioactive Shar-Pei.
Yeah. And whose fault is that,
huh, Francis?
Yeah, time to undo
what you did to this butterface.
Please, you should thank me.
Apparently, I made you immortal.
I'm actually quite jealous.
Yeah, but this ain't
a life worth living, is it?
Now, I'm about to do to you what Limp
Bizkit did to music in the late 90s.
Dad?
I think we can all agree that shit just
went sideways in the most colossal way.
Well, maybe not the most.
This is my most prized possession.
Wham?
No, no, no. Wham!
Make It Big is the album that George
and Andy earned the exclamation point.
So, am I supposed to just smile
and wave you out the door?
Think of it like spring cleaning.
Only if spring was death.
God, if I had a nickel for every time
I spanked it to Bernadette Peters.
Sounds like you do.
Bernadette is not going anywhere,
because you're not going anywhere.
Drink.
You're right. Cancer is only in my liver,
lungs, prostate, and brain.
All things I can live without.
You belong here at home.
Surrounded by your Voltron
and your Bernadette, and your me.
Listen, we both know
that cancer is a shit-show.
Like, a Yakov-Smirnoff-opening-for-the-
Spin-Doctors-at-the-Iowa-State-Fair shit-show.
And under no circumstances
will I take you to that show.
I want you to remember me.
Not the ghost of Christmas me.
Well, I wanna remember us.
I swear to God,
I will find you in the next life...
and I'm gonna boom-box Careless Whisper
outside your window.
Wham!
No one is boom-boxing shit. Okay?
We can fight this.
Besides, I just realized something.
You win. Your life is officially
way more fucked up than mine.
I love you.
Wade.
Weas.
You look like you need
a Blow Job and a shower.
Though courtesy calls
for the latter first.
How about three shots of Patrón?
Or how about Triticum aestivum, wheatgrass.
Excellent for the immune system.
Jesus Christ. You sound like Vanessa.
Here, check it out.
She's sending away for all these
colorful clinic brochures.
I'm sure they're all FDA approved.
Chechnya. Isn't that where you go
to get cancer?
You got China and Central Mexico.
You know how they say "cancer" in Spanish?
No.
El Cáncer.
I could have guessed that.
Look how happy you look here.
Mind if I keep this? Put it up,
so I can remember when you looked alive.
At least now I'm gonna win the dead pool.
Now that you're gonna die
tragically of cancer.
I got it, Weas. Thanks.
And that guy over there
came in looking for you.
Real Grim Reaper type.
I don't know. Might further the plot.
Boothe.
Wade.
Mr. Wilson.
How can I help you?
Besides luring children into a panel van.
I understand you've recently
been diagnosed with terminal cancer.
Stalker alert.
It's my job. Recruitment.
I'm sorry you've had such a tough go.
But you're a fighter. Special Forces.
41 confirmed kills.
One every seven weeks.
Same rate most folks get a haircut.
It's to wash the taste out.
It's tough to forget being so impressive.
And now you spend your days
sticking up for the little people...
People change. What do you want?
I represent an organization
that may be able to help.
What if I told you
we can cure your cancer?
And what's more, give you abilities
most men only dream of?
I'd say that you sound like an infomercial,
but not a good one, like Slap Chop.
More Shake Weight-y.
The world needs extraordinary soldiers.
We won't just make you better.
We will make you better than better.
A superhero.
Look, Agent Smith,
I tried the hero business and it left a mark.
But if I ever hit "fuck it,"
I'll look you up.
Shit. We're within 500 yards of a school,
so you may wanna...
His drink's on him.
What did he say?
Hey, what's going on?
Hey. Sorry.
I had a Liam Neeson nightmare.
I dreamt I kidnapped his daughter
and he just wasn't having it.
Hey, they've made three of those movies.
At some point you have to wonder
if he's just a bad parent.
The worst part about cancer
isn't what it does to you...
but what it does to the people you love.
Who knew if this guy could save my life...
but I knew there was only
one way that I could save hers.
Isn't that what superheroes do?
Okay. Let's pro-con this superhero thing.
Pro: They pull down a gaggle of ass.
Local dry cleaning discounts.
Lucrative film deals, both origin stories
and larger ensemble team movies.
Con: They're all lame-ass teacher's pets.
You know, I can hear you.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to them.
Stay right here.
You've been warned before, Deadpool.
This is a shameful and
reckless use of your powers.
You will both be coming with us.
Look, Colossus, I don't have time for the
goody two-shoes bullshit right now!
And you are?
Negasonic Teenage Warhead.
Negasonic Teenage...
What the shit?
That's the coolest name ever!
So, what, you're like, his sidekick?
No. Trainee.
Let me guess.
X-Men left you behind on what?
Shit detail?
What does that make you?
Pretending you're not here,
Negasonic Teenage Warhead.
Can we trade names?
Can we go?
Look! I'm a teenage girl.
I'd rather be anywhere than here.
I'm all about long sullen silences...
followed by mean comments,
followed by more silences.
So what's it gonna be, huh?
Long sullen silence...
or mean comment? Go on.
You got me in a box here.
We can't allow this, Deadpool.
Please, come quietly.
You big chrome cock-gobbler!
That's not nice.
You're really gonna fuck this up for me?
Trust me, that wheezing bag
of dick-tips has it coming.
He's pure evil.
Besides... nobody's getting hurt.
That guy was already up there
when I got here.
Wade, you are better than this.
- Join us. Use your powers for good.
- Heads up.
Be a superhero.
Listen!
The day I decide to become
a crime-fighting shit-swizzler...
who rooms with a bunch of other
little whiners at the Neverland mansion...
of some creepy, old, bald,
Heaven's Gate-looking motherfucker...
on that day...
I'll send your shiny,
happy ass a friend request.
But until then,
I'mma do what I came here to do.
Either that or slap the bitch outta you!
- Wade...
- Hey.
Zip it, Sinéad!
Hey, douche-pool!
And I hope you're watching...
Quite unfortunate.
That does it!
Canada!
That's not good.
Wade, please.
Cock shot!
Your poor wife.
You really should stop.
All the dinosaurs feared the T. rex.
I promise this gets worse for you, big boy!
This is embarrassing.
Please, stay down.
You ever hear of the one-legged man
in the ass-kicking contest?
Do you have off switch?
Yeah, it's right next to the prostate.
Or is that the on switch?
Enough!
Let us go talk to the Professor.
McAvoy or Stewart?
These timelines are so confusing.
"Dead or alive, you're coming with me!"
You will recover, Wade.
You always do.
You ever see 127 Hours? Spoiler alert.
Oh, my God.
Nasty.
There's the money shot, baby.
Are You There God? It's Me, Margaret.
Rock, meet bottom.
And when life ends up
breathtakingly fucked...
you can generally trace it back
to one big, bad decision.
The one that sent you
down the road to Shitsburgh.
This? Well, this was mine.
Mr. Wilson.
Nothing warms my heart more
than a change of someone else's.
You finally hit "fuck it."
Just promise you'll do right by me.
So I can do right by someone else.
Of course.
And please don't make the super-suit green.
Or animated.
Move it! Keep moving.
This place seems sanitary.
My first request is warmer hands.
And, Jesus, a warmer table.
We should really come up
with a safe word, fellas.
I'm thinking "pork and beans."
Easy.
Aren't you a little strong for a lady?
I'm calling wang.
What's up with the matches?
Oral fixation
or just a big Stallone fan?
Patience, Angel.
All in good time.
Are you here for the turndown service,
or what?
We have another talker.
I'm just excited about my first day
at superhero camp.
Shut the fuck up.
Mr. Wilson, my name's Ajax.
I manage this workshop.
My welcome speech used to be
full of euphemisms like...
"This may hurt a little."
"This may cause you some discomfort."
But I've grown blunt.
This workshop is not
a government-led program.
It's a private institution that turns
reclamation projects like yourself...
into men of extraordinary abilities.
But if you think superhuman powers
are acquired painlessly...
Wrong.
I'm injecting you with a serum that activates
any mutant genes lurking in your DNA.
For it to work we need to subject
you to extreme stress.
You've heard that whole
"make an omelet, break some eggs" bit, right?
I'm about to hurt you, Wade.
I was a patient here once myself, you know.
The treatment affects everyone differently.
It made Angel inhumanly strong.
In my case, it enhanced my reflexes.
Also scorched my nerve endings,
so I no longer feel pain.
And, in fact, I no longer feel anything.
Thanks! Thank you. Thank you.
You have something in your teeth.
Right in the middle there.
Just, I don't...
A little nugget of romaine lettuce
or something.
It's been bothering me for a long time.
Made you look.
Is Ajax your actual name?
Because it sounds suspiciously made up.
What is it really?
Kevin? Bruce? Scott?
Mitch? The Rickster?
Is it Basil Fawlty?
Joke away.
One thing that never survives this place
is a sense of humor.
We'll see about that.
I suppose we will.
He's all yours.
Come on.
You're gonna leave me all alone here
with less-angry Rosie O'Donnell?
This is how it's going to work.
Adrenaline acts as a
catalyst for the serum...
so we're going to have to
make you suffer.
If you're lucky, the mutant genes will activate
and manifest in a spectacular fashion.
If not, well, we'll have
to keep on hurting you...
in new and different ways,
each more painful than the last...
until you finally mutate.
Or die.
You mean like a bucket list?
Like a fuck-it list.
I'd really like to light a spliff
off the Olympic torch.
Pass it to me right after.
Let's not forget naked tandem base-jumping
with the WNBA's Sacramento Monarchs.
Anything on my bucket list
would involve public nudity.
Finally, giving Meredith Baxter-Birney
a Dutch oven.
No. Receiving a Dutch oven
from Meredith Baxter-Birney.
Making banana pancakes for my kids.
Vanessa.
I wanna see Vanessa.
You're lovely.
I don't know about anyone else,
but I'm touched.
We were just joking.
No, no. It's okay.
I encourage distractions.
Wouldn't want you giving up on us,
now would we?
Hey, don't take any shit from him,
Cunningham.
How tough can he be...
with a name like Francis?
Francis?
That's his legal name.
He got "Ajax" from the dish soap.
F-R-A-N-C-I...
Oops!
Snagged the dry cleaning tag
off your lab coat.
FYI, I could probably get you
the superhero discount.
You are so relentlessly annoying.
Thanks.
Never heard that before.
Why don't you do us all a favor
and shut the fuck up?
Or I'll sew your pretty mouth shut.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
See, here's the problem
with round-the-clock torture...
is that you can't really
step it up from there.
Is that what you think?
If this doesn't unlock your mutation,
then, well...
nothing will.
Now, what we're going to do is lower
the oxygen concentration in the air...
to the exact point you feel
like you're suffocating.
If your brainwaves slow,
meaning you're about to pass out...
then we'll turn up the O2.
If your heart rate slows...
meaning you're able to catch your breath...
we'll turn it back down.
And that's where we'll leave you.
Right there.
And I thought you guys were dicks before.
You know the funniest part of this?
You still think we're
making you a superhero.
You. A dishonorable discharge.
Hip-deep in hookers.
You're nothing.
Little secret, Wade.
This workshop doesn't make superheroes,
we make super-slaves.
We're gonna fit you with a control collar
and auction you off to the highest bidder.
Who knows what they'll have you doing?
Terrorizing citizens,
putting down freedom fighters.
Maybe just mow the occasional lawn.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're never going home after this.
Now there's a brave face.
Wait, wait! Wait. Wait.
Seriously, you actually have something
in your teeth now.
Enjoy your weekend.
"Weekend"? Back up.
Weekend?
Did I say this was a love story?
No, it's a horror movie.
Fucking hell.
Looks like someone lost his shot
at Homecoming King.
What have you done to me?
I've merely raised your stress levels
high enough to trigger a mutation.
You sadistic fuck!
I've cured you, Wade.
Now your mutated cells can heal anything.
It's attacking your cancer
as fast as it can form.
Yeah, I've seen similar
side effects before.
I could cure them...
but where's the fun in that?
Now, I'm gonna shut you in again, Wade.
Not because I need to.
Because I want to.
Oh, well.
Go ahead.
You smell like shit.
Motherfucker.
It's all right, it's all right.
I think we owe him that one, yeah?
You take off. Go on.
Off you go.
Quick question.
What's my name?
Didn't think so.
Sorry, Francis. My lips are sealed.
You don't want to kill me.
I'm the only one
who can fix your ugly mug.
What's my name?
Wade.
I didn't just get the cure to el cáncer...
I got the cure to el everything.
But there was only one thing...
that really mattered.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, that must hurt.
Thank you so much.
God, he's so fucking gnarly.
Look at his face.
Oh, my God. Poor guy.
Honey, don't stare.
Freak.
No way. I'm not making her life
as ugly as mine.
Come on, Wade, it can't be that bad.
Bullshit!
I'm a monster inside and out.
I belong in a fucking circus.
Wade, Vanessa loves you.
She doesn't care what you...
Do you like what you see?
No.
You look like an avocado had sex
with an older, more disgusting avocado.
Yeah.
Not gently. Like it was hate-fucking.
There was something wrong
with the relationship...
and that was the only catharsis that
they could find without violence.
And the only guy
who can fix this fugly mug...
is the British shitstick
who ran the mutant factory.
And he's gone. Poof!
Yeah, well you gotta do something
to remedy this...
because as of now,
you only have one course of action.
Damn straight.
- Find Francis.
- Star in horror films.
What?
Star in your own horror films.
Because you look like Freddy Krueger
face-fucked a topographical map of Utah.
Here's what I'm actually gonna do.
I'm gonna work through his crew
until somebody gives up Francis...
force him to fix this,
then put a bullet in his skull...
and fuck the brain hole.
I don't wanna see that
or think of it again.
But the douchebag does
think you're dead, right?
Yeah.
That's good.
You should keep it that way.
What, like, wear a mask?
Yes. A very thick mask.
All the time.
I am sorry...
you are haunting.
Your face is the stuff of nightmares.
Like a testicle with teeth.
You will die alone.
I mean, if you could die.
Ideally, for others' sake.
That'll do.
All you need now is a suit
and a nickname...
like Wade the Wisecracker...
or Scaredevil, Mr. Neverdie.
Shit.
What?
I put all my money on you and now...
I just realized I'm never gonna win the...
Dead pool.
Captain Deadpool.
No, just...
- Just Deadpool, yeah.
- Just Deadpool.
To you, Mr. Pool.
Deadpool.
That sounds like a fucking franchise.
This shit's gonna have nuts in it.
Where's Francis?
Seltzer water and lemon for blood.
Or wear red. Dumbass.
Don't make me ask twice.
Where...
is Francis?
He made me ask twice.
Is the mask muffling my voice?
Where's Francis?
Where the fuck is Francis?
You're about to be killed by a Zamboni.
Where's Francis?
No! Please!
Oh, God! I'm so sorry!
You little spider monkey!
Where... is... Francis?
This is confusing.
Is it sexist to hit you?
Is it more sexist to not hit you?
I mean, the line gets real... blurry.
WHERE IS FRANCIS?
Tell me where your fucking boss is
or you're gonna die!
In five minutes!
Don't hesitate to call me.
Nice to see you, Jared.
I'll take the footlong...
fully loaded.
41 confirmed kills.
Now it's 89. About to be 90.
Mr. Wilson?
You're looking very alive.
Only on the outside.
- This is not going to end well for me, is it?
- This is not gonna end well for you, no.
Where's your boss?
I can tell you exactly...
Oh, you'll tell me, but first...
You might wanna look away for this.
Now this little piggy went to...
Thank you, Agent Smith.
Taxi!
Hop in! Great day for a ride.
And we all know how this turned out.
Whoops! You weren't meant to see that.
There. All caught up.
We're here.
Sorry about bleeding in all your garbage.
Seltzer water and lemon for blood.
Some kinds of anger can't be managed...
like the kind where your year-long plan ends
with the wrong guy getting dismembered!
That said, when it comes time to licking
wounds, there's no place like home.
And I share that home with someone you've met,
the old blind lady from the laundromat, Al.
God, I miss cocaine.
Her.
Fourth-wall break
inside a fourth-wall break.
That's like 16 walls.
She's like Robin to my Batman,
except she's old, and black, and blind.
And I think she's in love with me.
Wait, pretty sure Robin loves Batman, too.
Al?
Morning, sleepyhead.
It smells like old lady pants in here.
Yes, I'm old. I wear pants.
But you're no lady.
So comfy.
Upside of being blind:
I've never seen you in Crocs.
You mean my big,
rubber masturbating shoes?
Yes, I know.
Downside of being blind...
I hear everything in this duplex.
Sit on a stick.
Bactin?
Yeah. Bactin should do it.
How's that Kullen coming along?
IKEA doesn't assemble itself, you know.
You're telling me.
I don't mind the Kullen.
It's an improvement on the Hurdal.
Please. Anything's an improvement
over the Hurdal.
I'd have taken an Hemnes
or a Trysil over the Hurdal.
No, I didn't get excited
till I saw the Kullen.
Screw, please.
Here? Now? Just kidding.
I know it's been decades.
You'd be surprised.
Pretty grossed out.
Ta... Da.
I wish I never heard of Craigslist.
And I quote, "Looking for roommate,
blind to life's imperfections.
"Must be good with hands."
Or would you rather
I build the IKEA, and you pay rent?
Why such a douche this morning?
Let's recap.
The cock thistle that turned
me into this freak...
slipped through my arms today...
Arm.
Catching him was my only chance to be
hot again, get my super sexy ex back...
and prevent this shit
from happening to someone else.
So, yeah, today was about as much fun
as a sandpaper dildo.
#driveby.
Found out who our friend
in the red suit is.
Fucking Wade Wilson.
Suppose I'd wear a mask, too
if I had a face like that.
I only wish I healed the same.
Still, we'll put him out of our misery.
On our terms.
Right. And when he heals?
He can't.
Not if there's nothing
left of him to heal.
You know, it's funny.
I almost miss the fucker.
I like a challenge.
But he's bad for business.
Now let's go find him.
Tylenol PM?
You can stick that
where you stuck the Bactin.
I raided my stash
of wisdom tooth Percocet...
and I am orbiting
fucking Saturn right now.
But I appreciate the gesture.
Am I crazy,
or is your hand really small?
About the size of a KFC spork.
I get why you're so pissy...
but your mood's never gonna brighten
till you find this woman...
and tell her how you feel.
What do I keep telling you, Mrs. Magoo?
She wouldn't have me.
If you could see me, you'd understand.
Looks aren't everything.
Looks are everything.
You ever heard David Beckham speak?
It's like he mouth-sexed
a can of helium.
Think Ryan Reynolds got this far
on his superior acting method?
Love is blind, Wade.
No.
You're blind.
So, you're just gonna
lie there and whimper?
No, I'm gonna wait till this arm
plows through puberty...
and then I'm gonna come up
with a whole new Christmas Day plan.
In the meantime,
you might wanna leave the room.
I bet it feels huge in this hand.
Go, go, go.
So, the doctor says, "The bad news is
you don't have that long to live."
So, the patient says,
"How long do I have?"
The doctor says, "Five."
The guy says, "Five what?"
The doctor says,
"Four, three, two..."
Can I help you ladies?
I do hope so.
I heard you might be able to point me
in the direction of a friend of mine.
Name of Wade Wilson.
Sorry.
I don't know the name.
Hey, you're not supposed to be
behind the bar.
I've seen this girl.
This must be Vanessa.
I've heard so much about you.
Sweetheart, you might wanna look around.
This isn't really the place
to do something like that.
Easy, Angel.
Put the little man down.
We have everything we need now.
You sure?
You don't want any clothes
that are not monochromatic?
Have fun at your midnight
showing of Blade II.
Thanks for having my back, guys.
Wade, we have a fucking problem.
And by "we," I mean "you."
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Is there a word for half afraid,
half angry?
Yeah, "afrangry," I guess.
Have you decided what
you're gonna say to her?
Fuck me!
Maybe not start with that.
Hey, coming onto our stage right now...
give it up for Chastity!
Or as I like to call her, Irony.
Better find her fast before numbnuts does.
How do you know she's in here?
Because I'm constantly stalking that fox.
Every time I see her,
it's like the first time...
Especially from this angle.
You can't buy love,
but you can rent it for three minutes.
You weak motherfucker!
Come on!
Come on, get it together.
This isn't about me, this is about Vanessa.
Here we go.
Maximum effort.
Vanessa.
Someone out back asking for you.
Something about an old boyfriend.
I knew it was you.
The weird, curvy edges.
Like a jigsaw puzzle.
You have Wade Wilson to thank for this.
Hey. Hey! Where'd she go?
I saw her head to the back.
Go get her, tiger.
Motherfucker!
- Wait, wait. Let's... Just...
- Cock juggling...
- We can talk about what we're gonna...
- Jiminy! Fuck face!
Okay, or you can hit that.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Fuck! Fuck!
- No, no. All right. Hey!
- Fuck!
- Hey.
Relax. Relax. Okay.
Okay. I think that's a good start.
I'm gonna rip his motherfucking...
Wait.
- Find it! Find it.
- What?
- I'm gonna get angry.
- Okay. All right.
All right. Okay. All right.
Here. This is Vanessa.
- What?
- No, wait. It's Francis.
He wants you to come to him.
- What is that?
- That's the shit emoji.
You know, it's the turd
with the smiling face and the eyes?
I thought it was chocolate yogurt
for so long.
I need guns.
Okay, which ones?
I need all the guns!
All right. Okay.
That's about 3,000 rounds.
We all know what I can do with 12.
Hey, hey, careful with that, Ronnie Milsap!
We're downrange.
I was gonna spend the night assembling the Börje,
but this is holding my interest.
I told you, we're going with the Urvaj,
not the Börje.
Get it through your head
or get out of fuck town.
Shit. That's all the pieces in the house.
Nah. Come on. Let's go.
Cough it up.
Up, up, up.
Down, down, down.
Fuck you.
.45 cal. I like it.
Wade...
I'd go with you, but I don't want to.
Listen, Al...
if I never see you again, I want you
to know that I love you very much.
And also, there's about 116 kilos of cocaine
buried somewhere in the apartment...
right next to the cure for blindness.
Good luck.
You wanna get fucked up?
Put her down over here.
Go on then.
Thanks, dickless. And I mean you.
Wow. You're a talker too. You and Wade.
I've been trying to tell you assholes,
you've got the wrong girl.
My old boyfriend, he's dead.
See, I thought that too.
But he keeps on coming back.
Like a cockroach...
but uglier.
Now, I may not feel, but he does.
Let's see how he fights
with your head on the block.
Ripley, from Alien 3!
Fuck, you're old.
Fake laugh. Hiding real pain.
Go get Silver Balls.
You guys going for a bite?
Early bird special?
Like there's something wrong with
eating before sundown or saving money.
No, you know that bad guy
that you let go?
He's got my girl.
You're gonna help me get her back.
Wade? Is that you?
Yeah, it's me, Deadpool,
and I got an offer that you can't refuse.
I'm gonna wait out here, okay?
It's a big house.
It's funny that I only ever see two of you.
It's almost like the studio
couldn't afford another X-Man.
And that is why, in my opinion...
the movie Cocoon
is pure pornography.
Who brought this twinkly man?
Twinkly, but deadly.
My chrome-penised friend back there
has agreed to do me this solid.
In exchange, I said that I would
consider joining his boy band.
It's not boy band.
Sure it's not.
So, any luck winning Gita back?
I tried to hold on tight, Mr. Pool...
but Bandhu is more craftier
and handsomer than me.
Well, I think you're pretty darn cute.
Dopinder?
What was that?
That was Bandhu in the trunk.
Ban who?
My romantic rival Bandhu.
He's tied up in the trunk.
I'm doing as you said, DP.
I plan to gut him like a tandoori fish,
then dump his carcass on Gita's doorstep.
I did not tell him to do that.
Absolutely not.
It got lost in translation.
Dopinder, this is no way
to win Gita's heart back!
I'm so proud of you.
Drop Bandhu off, safe and gentle-like.
Kill him.
And then, win Gita back...
the old fashioned way:
with your boyish charm.
Kidnap her.
He's super dead.
I presume a crisp high five?
For you? 10.
Okay, guys, let's get out there
and make a difference.
You know what to do.
Knock 'em dead, Pool Boy!
Time to make the chimi-fuckin'-changas.
Not often a dude ruins your face...
skull-stomps your sanity,
grabs your future baby mama...
and personally sees to four
of your five shittiest moments.
Let's just say, it's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas.
Hey.
Where's your duffle bag?
Bandhu?
Leave a message and have a happy day.
God damn it!
I'm gonna do this the old fashioned way...
with two swords and maximum effort.
Cue the music.
Wade Wilson!
What's my name?
I'mma fuckin' spell it out for ya.
Go get some.
Superhero landing.
She's gonna do a superhero landing.
Wait for it.
Superhero landing!
You know, that's really hard
on your knees.
Totally impractical. They all do it.
You're a lovely lady,
but I'm saving myself for Francis.
That's why I brought him.
I prefer not to hit a woman,
so please...
I mean, that's why I brought her?
Oh, no, finish your tweet.
It's not... That's...
Just give us a second. Yeah.
There you go. Hashtag it.
Go get her, tiger.
I so pity the dude who pressures
her into prom sex.
All right, then. Fire!
Finish fucking her the fuck up!
Language, please.
Suck a cock.
Look away, child.
Look away!
Wait!
Cease fire!
Fellas! Hey! Hey!
You only work
for that shit-spackled muppet fart.
So, I'mma give you a chance
for y'all to lay down your firearms...
in exchange for preferential,
bordering on gentle...
possibly even lover-like treatment.
Fine.
Commando!
Teabag!
Bob?
Wade?
Oh, my God, I haven't seen you since...
- Jacksonville. Fridays.
- Since TGI Fridays.
Well, what the hell!
God, come here, you.
How are the kids? Good?
And Gail?
She's still fixing that tuna casserole?
So good! But bad for the waistline,
if you know what I'm talking about.
Your... On the left.
You are beautiful woman.
That is so sweet.
Thanks.
Does he write you notes too?
He's such a romantic.
Don't worry, baby. I'm comin'.
Fire!
Hey!
Climb on!
Motherfucking...
Motherfucker should have worn
his brown pants.
You were right, beautiful.
Red really is my color.
Wade?
Don't worry, baby...
I'mma get you out of that shit-box.
What better way to crawl back inside
that head of yours?
Oh, you never left.
But you did, asshole!
Deep breath, darling.
Oh, wait.
Wrong choice of words.
I hope they blocked pain
to your every last nerve.
'Cause I'mma go lookin'!
I hear you grow back body parts now,
Wade.
When I'm finished...
parts will have to grow back you.
Good one.
Yep, that was a good one.
Let's dance.
And by dance, I mean...
let's try to kill each other.
Fine. Fists.
Sounds like your last Saturday night.
Asshole!
Hang in there, baby!
- Wade!
- I gotcha!
I got a plan. You're not gonna like it.
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Don't worry. I'm totally on top of this.
Damn it!
Maximum effort!
Thanks.
Just take it slow.
Oh, my God! That was so...
There are no words!
Me and you are headed
to fix this butterface.
What?
You stupid fucking idiot.
Did you really think
there was a cure... for that?
What?
You heard me.
No.
No!
So, you mean to say...
after all this, you can't fix me?
It sounds even stupider when you say it.
Like the kind of stupid who admits he can't
do the one thing I'm keeping him alive for?
Any last words?
What's my name?
Who fucking cares?
Wade!
Four or five moments.
I'm sorry?
Four or five moments,
that's all it takes.
To?
Be a hero.
Everyone thinks it's a full-time job.
Wake up a hero, brush your teeth a hero,
go to work a hero.
Not true.
Over a lifetime, there are only four
or five moments that really matter.
Moments when you're offered a choice.
To make a sacrifice, conquer a flaw,
save a friend...
spare an enemy.
In these moments...
everything else falls away.
The way the world sees us.
The way we...
Why?
You were droning on.
Sure, I may be stuck
looking like pepperoni flatbread...
but at least fuckface won't heal from that.
If wearing superhero tights...
means sparing psychopaths...
then maybe I wasn't meant to wear 'em.
Not everyone monitors a hall like you.
Just promise...
Yeah, yeah, I'll be on the lookout
for the next four moments.
Oh, shit.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm just a boy,
about to stand in front of a girl...
and tell her...
What the fuck am I gonna tell her?
Well, you better figure it out.
I can't even tell you...
I deserved that. That, too.
No, no, no, maybe not the nethers.
Start talking!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
For everything,
I'm sorry for leaving...
I'm sorry for not cowboying up sooner.
It's been rough couple of years.
Rough?
I live in a crackhouse.
With a family of 12.
Every night we spoon for warmth.
Everybody fights for Noelle.
She's the fattest.
There's nothing that we don't share.
Floor space, dental floss, even condoms.
So, you live in a house.
I should have come and found you sooner.
But, baby, the guy under this mask,
he ain't the same one that you remember.
You mean this mask?
And this one.
In case the other fell off.
All right. Yeah, just...
Like a Band-Aid, just give it a...
Owdie 5,000.
Wait, wait, wait...
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Wow.
Yeah.
Hey...
After a brief adjustment period...
and a bunch of drinks...
it's a face...
I'd be happy to sit on.
I'm not the same
underneath this suit, either.
No.
Super-penis.
Come on, Wade. Language.
Young one is present.
What are you still doing?
Get out of here.
Go make yourself useful!
You, go be a really big brother
to someone.
Tell Beast to stop shitting on my lawn.
And you, chicken noodle...
nothing compares to you.
Sinéad O'Connor, 1990. Sorry.
That's all right. You're cool.
What in the ass?
That was not mean!
I'm proud of you!
We will make an X-Man of you yet, Wade.
For a second there, it felt like
we were three mini-lion robots...
coming together to form one super robot.
There's a stupid.
Yeah.
And now, for the moment
I've all been waiting for.
Come here.
Wham! As promised.
See?
You don't need to be a superhero
to get the girl.
The right girl will bring
out the hero in you.
Now, let's finish this epic wide shot.
Pull out.
There we go, that looks nice.
That's gonna be about the only thing
that's pulling out tonight.
Who doesn't love a happy ending, huh?
Till next time, this is your friendly
neighborhood pool guy singing...
I'm never gonna dance again
the way I danced with you
You're still here?
It's over. Go home.
You're expecting a teaser for Deadpool 2.
Well, we don't have that kind of money.
What are you expecting?
Sam Jackson to show up?
With an eye patch
and a saucy little leather number?
Go. Go.
But I can tell you one thing,
and it's a bit of a secret.
For the sequel, we're gonna have Cable.
Amazing character.
Bionic arm, time travel.
We have no idea who we're gonna
cast yet, but it could be anybody.
Just need a big guy with a flat top.
Could be Mel Gibson, Dolph Lundgren...
Keira Knightley. She's got range.
Who knows.
Anyway, big secret.
And don't leave your garbage all lying around.
It's a total dick move.
Go.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org